sodmg.com 2011-06-04

# privacy - SODMG.com

### Privacy Policy

Date of Last Revision: February 5, 2009

This privacy policy governs the collection, storage and use of personal data collected by us, SouljaBoy. It provides you with details about the personal data we collect from you, how we use your personal data and your rights to control personal data we hold about you. Please read this privacy policy carefully – by accessing or browsing this website and network (the " **Services** "), you confirm that you have read, understood and agree to this privacy policy in its entirety. If you do not agree to this privacy policy in its entirety, you must not use the Services. 

This privacy policy was last updated on February 5, 2009. Please check back regularly to keep informed of updates to this privacy policy. 

#### Who we are

This social networking website is made available to you by SouljaBoy. We respect your right to privacy and will only process personal data you provide to us in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998, the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003 and other applicable privacy laws. 

If you have any questions about how we collect, store and use personal data, or if you have any other privacy-related questions, please click here to contact us. 

#### An important note about children

We do not and will not knowingly collect information from any unsupervised child under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, you may not use the Services unless you have the consent of, and are supervised by, a parent or guardian. 

#### The personal data we collect about you

When you access and browse the Services (including when you submit personal data to us through data entry fields on the Services), we may collect the following information from you: 

  1. Your name; 
  2. Your age, date of birth and sex; 
  3. Your postal address; 
  4. Your phone and e-mail details; 
  5. Your employment details (these are optional); 
  6. Your payment details if you choose to subscribe to or otherwise access paid-for content; and 
  7. Any other personal data that you choose to upload to or post on the Services, including blogs, photographs, messages, hobbies and interests and other personal details. 

In addition, we may collect anonymised details about visitors to our Services for the purposes of aggregate statistics or reporting purposes. However, no single individual will be identifiable from the anonymised details that we collect for these purposes. 

#### How we may store and use your information

We (or third party data processors acting on our behalf) may collect, store and use your personal data listed above for the following purposes: 

  1. to make the Services available to you and to provide you with content which is tailored to your individual tastes; 
  2. to complete any purchases you make through the Services and to provide you with services that you request; 
  3. to further develop and improve the Services; 
  4. to maintain and support any customer account that you have with us; 
  5. to include (or to permit the inclusion of) advertising within the Services of our own and third party products, services and promotions that we or they think may interest you; 
  6. where you have given us your consent, to contact you (including by SMS and e-mail) with products, services and promotions which we think may interest you; and 
  7. where you have given us your consent, to disclose your personal data to carefully chosen third parties so that they may contact you (including by SMS and e-mail) with products, services and promotions which they think may interest you. 

Other than as set out in this privacy policy, we will not disclose, sell or rent your personal data to any third party unless you have consented to this. If you do consent but later change your mind, you may contact us and we will cease any such activity. 

However, if a third party acquires all (or substantially all) of our business and/or assets, we may disclose your personal data to that third party in connection with the acquisition. 

We may also disclose your personal data where we are required to do so by applicable law, by order of a court, by a governmental body or by a law enforcement agency. We may also disclose your personal data in the context of investigating or reporting any issue arising in connection with activity by you or content supplied or purporting to be supplied by you, to you or on your behalf that we reasonably believe could be unlawful or otherwise in breach of our terms of service. 

#### Technology Licensor disclosures

We may also disclose your personal data to the business that provides us with technology infrastructure and hosting services for the Service (the " **Technology Licensor** "). The Technology Licensor will use your personal data in order to check that you are using the Services in a way that complies with applicable law, does not infringe the rights of any third party, to maintain and improve the infrastructure and hosting services that it provides to us, to serve advertising within the Services of third party products, services and promotions that it thinks may interest you and otherwise in accordance with its privacy policy. 

#### International transfers

We may transfer personal data that we collect from you to third parties (including the Technology Licensor) located in countries that are outside of the European Economic Area where necessary to exercise, or in connection with, the uses of your data described above. Please be aware that countries which are outside the European Economic Area may not offer the same level of data protection as the United Kingdom, although our collection, storage and use of your personal data will continue to be governed by this privacy policy. 

#### Cookies

This website uses cookies to collect information about you. Cookies are small data files which are placed on your computer by this website and which collect certain personal data about you. This enables us to tailor our service offering (including the website) to provide you with products and services which are more relevant to your individual tastes. However, you may change your website browser settings to reject cookies, although please note that if you do this it may impair the functionality of the Services. As each website browser is different, please visit your browser's "Help" menu to learn how to change your cookie preferences. 

#### Security

Whilst we take appropriate technical and organisational measures to safeguard the personal data that you provide to us, no transmission over the Internet can ever be guaranteed secure. Consequently, please note that we cannot guarantee the security of any personal data that you transfer over the Internet to us. 

#### Your rights

You have the following rights: 

  1. the right to ask us to provide you with copies of personal data that we hold about you at any time, subject to a fee specified by law (currently £10); 
  2. the right to ask us to update and correct any out-of-date or incorrect personal data that we hold about you free of charge; and 
  3. the right to opt out of any marketing communications that we may send you. 

If you wish to exercise any of the above rights, please e-mail us at the address specified above. 

#### Third party sites

This website also contains links to other third party websites over which we have no control. Please note that this privacy policy applies only to the personal data that we collect through this website and we cannot be responsible for personal data that third parties may collect, store and use through their independent websites. You should always read the privacy policy of each website you visit carefully.
